Stocks and bonds are moving higher....
주식과 채권이 오르고...
왜 증권방송을 봐?
Why are we watching
the Business Channel?
내 이니셜과 똑같은 'MEG'란
주식을 봤거든
Because the other day I saw there was
a stock with my initials, MEG, on it.
Sometimes it takes two or three hours
before it comes up again.
한 번 화면에 뜨는 데
두세 시간은 걸리지만
But when it does, it's exciting.
일단 뜨면 정말 멋져
Okay, honey, you really need a job.
너 얼른 직장 구해야겠다
아빠가 직장을 알아봐 줄
사람을 소개해 주신대
Dad says he knows someone
you can call for an interview.
어머, 저것 봐!
오늘 벌써 세 번째 징조야!
Right there! That's the third
sign today. Right there.
On behalf of everyone,
I'd just like to say, "Huh?"
모두를 대표해서 묻겠는데
뭔 소리야?
No, you just said "dad."
And everywhere I go today...
'아빠'란 소리를 했잖아
종일 들었거든
... I keep getting signs
telling me to go see my father.
이건 아빠를 만나 보라는
신의 계시라고
Like when I was walking over here
and I passed a buffet.
오늘은 뷔페 식당 앞을
지나왔는데
아빠 성하고 비슷하잖아
Which is my father's last name.
And they were serving franks...
'프랭크스'를 먹던데
'스'만 빼면 아빠 이름이고
...which is his first name
minus the "s" at the end.
And there was a rotisserie
with a spinning chicken.
또 꼬챙이에 끼워 돌리는
통닭도 봤어
His lndian name?
아빠의 인디언 이름이야?
No. Because I chickened out
the last time...
아니, 전에 내가 겁먹은 닭처럼
막판에 포기했잖아
...when I tried to meet him.
So coincidences? I don't think so.
아빠 만나러 갔을 때 말야
이건 절대 우연이 아니라고
- 무서워라
- 거의 엽기야
-Very freaky.
-Eerie.
남은 햄버거 누가 먹을래?
Who wants the last hamburger?
바로 그거야
아빠를 만나 봐야겠어
That's it.
Now I have to go see him.
Why?
왜?
맥도널드 햄버거잖아
Hamburger? McDonald's?
맥도널드 할아버지처럼
우리 아빠도 늙으셨어
Old McDonald had a farm.
My dad is a pharmacist.
The One With the Bullies
Man, I am so beat.
피곤해 죽겠어
You wanna forget racquetball
and hang out?
- 오늘 라켓볼 하루 쉴까?
- 좋지
Yeah, all right.
거기 우리 자리야
-Hey, you're in our seats.
-Sorry, we didn't know.
- 미안, 몰랐거든
- 우리가 먼저 앉았어
We were sitting there.
Okay.
There is one more way to say it.
단도직입적으로 묻겠는데
그걸 어떻게 믿어?
Who knows it?
지금 농담 따먹기 해?
-Was that supposed to be funny?
-Actually, I was going for colorful.
땅 따먹기 한 건데
-What's with this guy?
-What's with you?
- 이 자식 왜 이래?
- 너 뭐야?
Nothing. Nothing's with him.
아니, 멀쩡한 친구라고
커피 맛있게 마셔
Enjoy your coffee.
What just happened?
방금 무슨 일이 일어났지?
I just took your hat.
See, I can be funny too.
내가 장난삼아 네 모자를
빼앗았지
My joke is that I took your hat.
나도 웃길 줄 알거든
웃겨 죽겠네
That is funny.
Can I have it back?
- 얼른 돌려줘
- 안 돼
- 안 된다고?
- 안 돼!
알았어, 이제 알았다고
너 아주 웃겨
You know what?
I think you're very funny.
Kudos on that hat joke.
코미디언 해도 되겠어
But come on, guys,
just give him back the hat.
이제 모자 돌려줘
Why should we?
우리가 왜?
Because it's a special hat.
특별한 모자니까
He bought it because
he was feeling down one day.
이 친구가 울적한 기분을
풀려고 샀던 모자거든
So he got the hat...
...to cheer himself up, you know?
- 챈들러, 네가...
- 나한테 떠넘기지 마
-Chandler
-Stop talking. Stop talking now.
Let me get this straight.
You're stealing my hat?
그러니까 지금 내 모자를
훔치는 거야?
You got a problem?
- 그래서 불만이야?
- 아니, 확실하게 해두려고
I just want to make sure
we're on the same page.
How'd the interview go?
면접 어떻게 됐어?
It bit.
꽝이야
It was a 50s theme restaurant.
50년대 풍의 식당인데
I'd have to cook in a costume
and dance on the counter.
그 시절 옷을 입고 요리하고
춤도 춰야 한대
난 정식 요리사야
I was a sous chef
at Cafe des Artistes.
그런 데서 가짜 가슴 붙이고
일할 순 없다고!
How can I take a job where I have
to make Laverne-and-Curly Fries?
-Don't do it.
-How can I not do it?
- 그럼 하지 마
- 어떻게 안 해?
은행에 겨우 127달러뿐인데!
I have $127 in the bank!
모니카, 진정하고
맥주나 가져와
Monica, relax. Go get a beer.
안 마셔!
I don't want a beer.
누가 너더러 마시래?
Who said it was for you?
안녕
왜 죽을상이야?
What's the matter?
Some mean guys at the coffeehouse
took my hat.
어떤 남자가 카페에서
내 모자를 빼앗았어
- 어머!
- 정말이야?
-No!
-You're kidding?
깡패 같은 놈들이었어
진짜 깡패 말야
It was ridiculous.
These guys were bullies.
Actual bullies.
어른이 되어서도
이런 일이 생기다니
We're grownups. This kind of stuff
isn't supposed to happen anymore.
Oh, no, wait a minute.
I have no one.
난 위로해 줄 사람도 없네
Let's go down there
and get your hat back.
당장 가서 되찾아오자
됐어, 벌써 팔아먹었겠지
Forget it. It's probably stripped
and sold for parts by now.
- 나 올라갔어!
- 뭐?
-I went up!
-What?
My stock, MEG, it went up two points.
내 주식 MEG말이야
2포인트나 올라갔어
어제 내 전 재산
127달러를 몽땅 투자했다면...
Do you realize that if I'd invested
my $127 in myself yesterday...
...that l'd, like, have
a lot more than that today.
돈 좀 벌었을 텐데
You know what?
I'm going to do it.
정말 그래야겠어
- 뭘?
- 돈을 투자해 보는 거야!
-Do what?
-Put all my money in me.
넌 주식의 '주'자도 모르잖아
You don't know a thing
about the stock market.
사고 팔고 오리고 내리고
강세, 약세만 알면 되잖아
What's to know?
Buy, sell. High, low. Bears, bulls.
Yes, Manhattan.
네, 맨해튼이요
전화번호 좀 알려 줘요
주식을... 파는 가게요
Telephone number for the stock...
...selling store.
See? I told you these pillows
would be a good idea.
내가 베개 가져오자고
하길 잘했지?
Oh, God.
맙소사!
Here we go.
바로 여기야
For the first time in my life,
I'm gonna say, "Hi, Birth Father!"
난생 처음으로 이럴 거야
'안녕, 친아빠! '
- 우리가 응원해 줄게
- 행운을 빌어
-We love you. We're here for you.
-Good luck.
Thanks.
고마워
샌드위치 먹을래?
Hey, Rach, you want some sandwich?
안에 뭐가 들었어?
What is in that?
Olive loaf and ham spread. No mayo.
올리브 빵하고 햄
마요네즈는 안 발랐어
마요네즈 안 넣기 잘했네
덜 느끼할 테니
No, because mayo,
that would make it gross.
안녕?
- 도망쳐, 피비!
- 이러지 마, 강아지야
-Run, Phoebe, run!
-No, no, doggy, please!
I do so want to love all animals.
Please, no. Back off!
난 동물 애호가라고
저리 가!
-You got a bone?
-Are you kidding?
- 뼈다귀 있어?
- 내 갈비뼈?
저리 가라니까!
Look, kibbles! Bits!
내 다리에서 떨어져
이 더러운 똥개야!
Get the hell off my leg,
you yippity piece of crap!
Okay. All right. We have a problem.
문제가 생겼어
Why don't you take his trampoline?
나가서 쟤 좀 말려 봐
Okay, here, I know what we can do.
- 방법이 있어
- 안 돼!
Okay, doggy, get the sandwich!
가서 샌드위치 먹어!
어서 샌드위치를 먹어
착하기도 하지
Go get the sandwich!
Good doggy. Get the sandwich!
굶어 죽게 생겼는데도
저 샌드위치는 안 먹네?
The dog will lick himself
but he will not touch your sandwich.
What does that tell you?
-lf he's not going to eat it, I will.
-Are you crazy?
- 그럼 다시 가져올래
- 미쳤어?
강아지 갖고 뭘 그래?
He's just a little dog.
-Hey.
-What?
- 로스
- 왜?
Do you have to be a Century 21
real-estate agent...
그런 멋진 재킷을 입다니
잘나가는 부동산업자인가?
...to get to wear those cool jackets?
Do you say this stuff to girls?
왜, 반했냐?
네 모자를 쓰고 다니던
그 친구 아냐?
Isn't that the guy
who used to wear your hat?
우리 자리에 앉았네
And look where they're sitting.
You're joking, right?
You guys just walked through the door.
지금 농담해?
방금 들어왔잖아
Maybe we didn't make it clear enough.
우리 말을 못 알아듣나 봐
This couch belongs to us.
이건 우리 소파야
I'll tell you what,
you call the couch...
이렇게 하자고
서로 '소파야' 하고 불러서
...and then we'll call the couch...
...and we'll see who it comes to.
어느 쪽으로 오나 보자고
You know, I keep wondering
why you two are still sitting here.
정말 궁금하네
아직도 자리 안 비켰어?
더는 못 참아!
All right, that's it.
I have had enough of this.
도가 지나치잖아, 건터!
Gunther.
These guys are trying
to take our seat.
이 사람들이 우리 자리를
빼앗으려고 해요
저분들이 먼저 왔어요
Fellas, these guys were here first.
- 미안해요
- 우리가 그걸 몰랐네
Oh, sorry, didn't realize.
There you go.
- 됐지?
- 고마워요, 건터
Thank you, Gunther.
We didn't want to have
to go and do that.
우리 손까지 더럽히긴 싫어
He told on us?
우리한테 한 말이야?
You told on us?
- 우리한테 그랬냐고?
- 누가 계속 귀찮게 하래?
Well, pal, you didn't
give me much of a choice.
-Don't play with his thing.
-I know.
- 목걸이는 건드리지 마
- 알았어
All right.
좋아, 나가서 한판 뜨자
Let's take this outside.
나가서 한판 뜨자고?
"Let's take this outside?"
Who talks like that?
요즘도 저런 말 쓰냐?
The guy who's about to kick your ass
talks like that.
너희 엉덩이를 걷어차 줄
사람들이 쓰는 말이지
You had to ask.
- 꼭 알고 싶어서 물었어?
- 그러게
Okay, okay, look. See...
좋아, 좋다고
너희들과 싸우긴 싫어
...the thing is, we're not gonna
fight you guys.
Here's the deal.
그럼 이렇게 해
You won't have to, so long as you
never ever show your faces here again.
여기 다시 안 나타나면
우리랑 싸울 필요가 없지
I think you played
the Gunther card too soon.
너 건터를 너무 빨리
써먹은 것 같아
Hey, Pheebs, I think you're good to go.
피비, 이제 들어가도 되겠어
Yeah, I don't know.
모르겠어
What's the matter?
왜 그래?
I just think that this was
a really bad sign.
나쁜 징조인 것 같아
야수가 가로막는다니
Like the beast at the threshold.
내겐 할머니를 빼면
가족이 없잖아
It's just I have no family left,
except for my grandmother.
할머니도 영원히 내 곁에
계실 수는 없고
But let's face it, she's not
gonna be around forever.
Despite what she says.
할머니는 그런다고 하시지만
And I have a sister who I've barely
spoken to since we shared a womb.
엄마 자궁을 떠난 이후로
말도 않는 쌍둥이 빼고
내 유일한 친아빠잖아
I don't know. This is my real father...
...and I want things to be,
like, just right.
잘됐으면 좋겠다고
- 네 말 충분히 알겠어
- 네가 뭘 하든 다 이해해
I completely understand.
Whatever you need.
Hey, you want to go home?
그냥 집에 갈까?
Okay, thanks. Sorry, again.
그래, 고마워
또 미안하게 됐어
What was that?
무슨 소리였지?
I'm guessing the threshold's clear now.
집 앞을 지키던
야수가 사라진 것 같아
'SGJ' 주식 다섯 주요
당장 사 줘요
I want to buy five shares of SGJ.
Now.
Come on, time is money, my friend!
시간은 돈이라고요!
Thank you!
고마워요
"Time is money, my friend?"
시간이 돈이라고?
이렇게 말했어야지
You missed
"Takes money to make money"...
...and "Don't make me come down there
and kick your Wall Street butt."
'돈 놓고 돈 먹기야!
쫓아가기 전에 말들어! '
I made $ 17 before breakfast.
What have you done?
오전에만 17달러 벌었어
넌 뭘 했지?
여기서 아침 먹으면서
3달러 50센트 굳혔지
I had breakfast here,
so technically I saved $3.50.
How did you make $17?
어떻게 17달러나?
말해 주지, 내 궁핍한 친구
Well, my financially
challenged friends...
'CHP'와 'ZXY'에
분산투자를 했거든
...I split my money and I bought
some shares of CHP and ZXY.
How come those?
왜 그 회사들을?
'CHP'는 내가 좋아하는 가수가
나온 방송국이고
Well, CHP because I used to have a
crush on Erik Estrada.
'ZXY'는 왠지 섹시하잖아
And ZXY because I think
it sounds "zexy."
'MEG'는 어쩌고?
What happened to MEG?
MEG was good for me, but I dumped her.
'MEG'도 괜찮았는데
헐값에 넘겼어
'넘어지기 전에 떠나라'
이게 내 신조거든
My motto is, "Get out
before they go down."
That is so not my motto.
난 그 반대로 하는데
강아지는 어때?
How's the dog?
Okay. I talked to the vet.
People are so nice upstate.
수의사하고 통화했는데
사람들이 정말 친절해
He said the little fella's gonna be
okay, and I can get him tomorrow.
강아지는 무사하니까
내일 데려가래
- 다행이네
- 정말 잘됐어
-Good.
-Thank God.
상처가 심해서 많이 꿰맸고
But he did have to have
a bunch of stitches.
개의 귀가 다시 자라는 건
드문 경우지만
And he said that only once in a blue
moon does a dog's ear grow back.
희망은 가져야지
So still hoping.
Now are you going to call your dad
to let him know that his dog is okay?
그럼 아빠에게 전화해서
강아지가 무사하다고 해야지
I don't want to meet my father
over the phone.
전화를 통해서 아빠를
만나기는 싫어
What will I say,
"Hi, I'm the daughter you abandoned.
뭐라고 하지?
'아빠가 버린 딸인데
제가 개를 작살냈어요'
Oh, by the way, I broke your dog."
Hey, Pheebs, if you want, I'll do it.
그럼 내가 전화할까?
그래
내 얘기는 절대 하지 마
Listen, just don't say anything
about me, okay?
Don't...
안 돼!
... be too long with the phone.
통화는 간단히, 알았지?
주식시장 폐장하면
정상으로 돌아올 거야
She'll be a much better friend
once the market closes.
It's a woman.
- 여자가 받았어
- 얘기해
So talk to her.
안녕하세요, 부페이 부인
Hello, Mrs. Buffay.
개의 행방을 압니다
I know where your dog is.
24시간 내에 멀쩡한 모습으로
돌아갈 겁니다, 끊을게요
I want you to know he'll be returned
to you almost as good as new...
...within 24 hours.
Goodbye.
-Why the voice?
-Hard to say.
- 목소리가 왜 그래?
- 알면 다쳐
- 네 카푸치노 나왔어
- 고마워
Your cappuccino, sir.
Thank you.
-This is better than the coffeehouse.
-Absolutely.
- 카페보다 여기가 훨씬 낫다
- 그럼
How come it's not mixing
with the water?
왜 물이랑 안 섞이지?
끊임없이 저어 줘야 한대
젖고 마시고... 멈추면 안 돼
The package says to keep it moving.
Stir and drink, never let it settle.
This is ridiculous.
정말 한심하네
조카 세례식에 다녀와서
After I get back from
my niece's christening...
...I'll go to the coffeehouse with you
and we'll have a cup of coffee.
함께 카페에 가서
커피를 마시자고
No problem. Joey's there.
걱정 마, 조이가 있잖아
좋아!
싫어!
- 싫다고?
- 싫어!
커피를 마실 때마다
조이를 대동하긴 싫다고
I don't want to have to have Joey with
me every time I want decent coffee.
이런 엉터리 카푸치노를
평생 마시기도 싫고!
And I don't want to drink
cappuccino with a "k."
우리 둘이 가서
당당히 맞서는 거야
I say you and I go
and stand up to those guys.
잠깐 진정하게나, 친구
All right, hang on
a second there, Custer.
Ross, have you ever
been beaten up before?
- 전에 맞아 본 적 있어?
- 그럼!
Yeah, sure.
By someone besides Monica?
- 모니카 말고
- 그럼 없어
좀 맞으면 어때? 남자로서
한 번은 겪을 일이잖아
So what?
So we get beaten up. Maybe that's
something a man has to go through.
성인식 같은 통과의례라고
Like a rite of passage or something.
다시 총각딱지 떼면 안 될까?
Couldn't we just lose
our virginities again?
내 총각딱지가 다시 자라거든
Because I think actually
mine's growing back.
-I need $100.
-What?
- 100달러만 빌려 줘
- 뭐?
어서 들어와
Welcome home.
- 100달러만 빌려 줘
- 뭐 하려고?
-I need $100.
-For what?
- 다시 주식을 하려고
- 언제 그만뒀어?
-To get back in the game.
-When did you get out?
I lost it all. I lost it.
전부 다 잃었어
생각해 봤는데
너도 투자를 해야 돼
I've come to terms with it,
you have to, too.
좋아
Look, Mon, I'm really sorry.
정말 유감이야, 모니카
Where are we on the $100?
100달러는?
I don't have it.
- 나 돈 없어
- 당장 필요해!
But I need it!
안 그러면 그 식당에
나가야 한다고
Otherwise, I'll have to
take that diner job.
이상한 옷을 입고
춤추는 곳 말이야
You know, with the dancing
and the costumes.
I don't want to have to wear
flame-retardant boobs.
불연성 인공 가슴을 달고
일하긴 싫다고
그럼, 당연하지
Nobody does, honey.
- 안녕하세요
- 누들!
Noodle!
우리 누들이 어떻게 된 거죠?
Oh, my God. What the hell
happened to my dog?
사고였어요
It was an accident.
고의로 개를 잡을 여잔 아니죠
채식주의자거든요
And the woman who did this
would never hurt a dog on purpose.
She's a vegetarian.
꿰맸어요?
Are these stitches?
네, 8바늘이요
개 기준으론 56바늘이죠
Yeah, eight of them.
That's 56 to him.
If it's raining, you can't
let him look up...
비오면 그 통에 물차니까
하늘을 못 쳐다보게 하세요
... because that cone
will fill up fast.
어쨌거나 데려다 줘서
고마워요
Thanks for bringing back
what's left of him.
프랭크 집에 있어요?
-ls Frank home?
-How do you know Frank?
프랭크를 알아요?
예전에 알던 사이에요
지금 있나요?
Just from a long time ago.
Is he here?
그래요
- 프랭크!
- 네!
뭐예요?
What?
프랭크 아버지 말이었어요
I mean Frank Senior.
He went out for groceries.
장보러 갔어요
금방 오시나요?
Will he be back soon?
He left four years ago.
We're expecting him back any minute.
4년 전에 갔으니까
금방 오겠죠
전 갈게요
개 그렇게 돼서 죄송해요
I'm gonna go.
I'm sorry about the dog.
Everything.
I'm sorry.
아가씨! 잠깐만요!
Hey, lady!
Hey, wait up!
-How do you know my dad?
-Well, I don't really.
우리 아빠를 어떻게 알죠?
잘은 몰라
피가 끌리는 거지
Just genetically.
He's kind of my dad too.
내 아빠이기도 하거든
Heavy.
- 죽이네
- 그래
So did he ever talk about me... Phoebe?
내 이름은 피비인데
아빠가 내 얘기했었니?
아니, 원래 말이 없었어
No, but he didn't really talk
about anything.
Except stilts.
목마 얘기만 했지
-Stilts?
-Yeah, he loved stilts.
- 목마?
- 목마를 좋아했거든
하루는 엄마 지갑에서
담배를 훔치고 있는데
One time, I was upstairs stealing
cigarettes out of my mom's purse...
창가로 아빠 머리가
들썩이는 게 보이더라고
...and all of a sudden I look over...
...and there's Dad's head,
bobbing past the window.
큰 웃음을 지으면서
손을 흔들고 있었지
He just had this big smile on his face
and he was waving...
...because he was happiest
when he was on his stilts.
목마를 탈 때
가장 행복해 했거든
I don't know what to do with that.
나라면 황당했을 거야
나도 그랬어
Me neither.
So are you, like, my big sister?
- 그럼 내 누나?
- 그래
정말 신난다
내게 맥주도 사 주고!
This is huge. You can buy me beer!
I'm not gonna.
꿈 깨라
뭐가 좋은지 알아?
But you know what's cool? If you had
a friend named Pete, I could say...
'피트는 내 동생 친구야'
이렇게 말할 수 있잖아
... "I know Pete.
He's friends with my brother."
-I got a friend named Mark.
-That'll work too.
- 마크란 친구가 있는데
- 그 이름도 괜찮고
Cool. All right.
좋아
So maybe, you know,
I could give you a call sometime.
언제 전화해도 괜찮아?
이런저런 얘기도 하고
We could talk or something.
-Yeah, that'd be okay.
-All right.
- 괜찮을 것 같아
- 좋아
- 전화번호부에 번호 나와
- 알았어
I'm in the book.
목마라고?
So stilts, huh?
아빠가 빗물 통에
머리 박은 자국 보여 줄까?
If you want, I can show you where
he hit his head on the rain gutter.
좋아
우린 해냈어
진지를 사수하러 왔잖아
We did it. We're here.
We are standing our ground.
-How long does coffee take?
-Would you come on? Come on!
- 커피가 왜 이리 안 나오지?
- 서둘러요!
고마워요
Thank you.
-There we go.
-I think we proved our point.
- 다 마셨어
- 소기의 목적은 달성했군
-You burn your mouth?
-Cannot feel my tongue.
- 입 데었어?
- 혀에 감각이 없어졌어
깡패 출현!
Bullies! Big bullies!
이게 누구야?
겁쟁이들이 나타났군
Look who's here.
It's the weenies.
요전에 우리가 알아듣게
얘기했을 텐데?
Did we not make ourselves clear
the other day?
그래서 온 거야
That's why we're here.
Yes, we're standing our ground.
우린 절대 물러나지 않아
지금도 가만있잖아
Apparently.
- 좋아, 붙어 보자고
- 뭐야, 무기 꺼내?
Let's do this already.
You got a weapon?
A nice watch.
I don't want to break it on your ribs.
비싼 시계인데
네 갈비에 깨질까 봐
좋아, 붙어 보자고
All right, let's do this.
Question: If I don't care about
my watch, can I use it as a weapon?
질문 있는데
시계가 싸구려라면
무기로 써도 괜찮아?
무슨 소리야?
-What do you mean?
-It's sharp, it's metal.
날카로운 금속성이잖아
데미지를 줄 수 있다고
I think I can do some
serious damage with it.
- 시계 사용은 안 돼
- 좋아
No, you can't use your watch.
Or your keys.
- 열쇠도 안 되고
- 좋아
Here's what we'll do.
이렇게 하자고
열쇠와 시계를 담아서
저기 올려놓자고
We'll put all keys and watches
in the hat over there.
All right?
All right, come on, man. Let's do it!
이번에 진짜 덤벼!
궁금해서 물어보는데
얼굴도 때리기야?
Before I forget, are we hitting faces?
당연하지, 그건 왜?
Of course. Why wouldn't you hit faces?
난 월요일에 아주 중요한
발표를 해야 하거든
I have to work on Monday.
I have a big presentation.
Actually, I gotta show
this apartment tomorrow...
내일 아파트 보여 주러
다녀야 하는데
...and this no-faces thing
might not be a bad idea.
괜찮은 생각인 것 같아
좋아, 목 위로는
때리지 않기
Nothing from the neck up.
허리 아래도 안 되고
Or the waist down.
-Dana's ovulating.
-Really? You guys trying again?
- 다나가 배란기거든
- 아기 가지려고?
Let me get this straight.
We're talking about the middle?
헷갈려서 말인데
가운데만 때리는 거야?
덤벼!
Come on!
나랑 한판 붙고 싶어?
어서 덤벼 보라고!
You want a piece of this?
I'm standing here!
우리 시계를 훔쳐갔어!
Those guys are taking our stuff!
God, that was amazing.
That was incredible.
정말 죽여줬어!
멋졌다고!
-You guys kicked butt!
-Us? What about you guys?
- 멋지게 해치웠어
- 너희도 도왔잖아
덩치도 큰 녀석인데
한 방에 날려 버렸잖아
You really gave it to
old Mr. Clean back there.
-He was a big guy.
-Yeah, he was, wasn't he?
- 그건 그래
- 난 못 봐서 모르겠다
I wouldn't know,
having missed everything.
자학하지 마
Don't do that to yourself.
Any one of us could have tripped
over that little girl's jump rope.
우리도 그 꼬마의 줄넘기에
걸려 넘어질 수 있었어
So listen, guys...
그럼 우리...
이제 괜찮은 거야?
...are we okay here?
- 그럼
- 좋았어
We're okay.
그럼 내 모자 돌려줄래?
So can I have my hat back?
싫어
Oh, my God. Look at her.
맙소사, 모니카 좀 봐
안녕, 모니카?
Hi, Monica!
- 할 만해?
- 가슴 정말 빵빵하다!
How's it going?
Hey, nice boobs.
얘들아, 잘 보라고
Guys, guys. Check this out.
멋져!
Excellent.